plugmod.com 2009-12-31

# ConsoleShop.com: Privacy Statement

ConsoleShop.com respects your privacy. ConsoleShop.com does not sell, rent or loan any personal information that is identifiable to any unrelated third parties. Any personal information given to ConsoleShop.com will be held with the utmost care and security and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. In short, your identity will always be kept anonymous. ConsoleShop.com requires certain name information as well as email addresses for submitting online comments. Therefore, if you don't want your comments or concerns to be viewed by any or all visitors, be advised not to submit them. ConsoleShop.com reserves the right to edit or remove anything posted to the website that in our sole discretion is deemed to be offensive, illegal or inappropriate in any way whatsoever. 

ConsoleShop.com believes strongly that all personal information of users and customers must be kept private and deserves protection. You can navigate and visit the website without registering or providing any personal information. However, ConsoleShop.com does require certain personal information and shipping address information for the processing of orders. 

**How do I know my credit card and personal information is secure?**   
All personal information and credit card information in the order process is completed using a secure server. ConsoleShop.com makes use of newest Secure Socket Layers (SSL) to encrypt all data provided by the customer. ConsoleShop.com makes every possible effort, given today's technology, to ensure your personal and credit card information is kept safe and private. 

**Will personal information be disclosed to any other parties?**   
Under ConsoleShop.com policy, no personal information is sold or made available to any other person or party outside of the ConsoleShop.com team.
